WHAT?
WHAT THE
I BOUGHT A STILETTO comb on amazon.de
and today I'm going to unbox it and of
course review it.
So
I've got the package. I've got the
package. Okay guys, so this is the
Amazon package that it was delivered in.
Uh it's stiletto comb if you want it
just go into the description.
I'm so dumb. Okay, so Uh
I just crossed out some of the personal
information so you guys don't know where
I live cuz you know since I'm so famous
everyone will want to come to my house.
Okay, so um yeah, I've already opened it
just to make sure that there's no other
personal information here.
Uh there's only this box in here which
I've already looked at. And this is the
only personal information that is still
on the box.
See it? I don't know what it says on
there. It's kind of it's ripped off so
is that itch blade comb part what part?
Patin and that looks like Chinese to me.
I'm not sure.
That that's a good way to mean it.
Also uh I've actually got some footage
of the postman arriving and giving me
this amazing package in the crate. So uh
yeah, if you want to see that I'll just
quickly show it here.
Okay.
This seems to be
uh the house uh Spinjitzu.
FedEx. And so yeah.
Let's open this thing.
Oh, okay. That wasn't the best opening.
Okay, so this is the
thing.
Let's put that over there. Just make
sure there's nothing else in the
package. Okay.
Goodbye.
And so this is the knife comb, I guess.
So, uh it looks like there's actually a
screw missing there. I'm not sure if you
can
see that. Of course, you can see that.
And I'm not sure if that's part of the
design or whatever.
But, the rest of the screws are in as
well. So, yeah.
Uh I don't know how you open this.
I I guess it's one of the buttons here.
Okay, this one goes down. 3 2 1
Wait.
Oh, there's a pin here.
Okay, so
That is so violent when it opens. Just
watch this.
Let me put that in slow motion quickly.
Okay.
Okay, so uh I guess
it opens pretty well.
And I guess to put And to put it back
in, you just
push that down.
Then, you can just put it back there.
So, I guess you just
Yeah, so that's kind of cool.
It's pretty straight.
If you can see that, guys. Pretty
straight.
It's also made out of hard steel, which
is pretty cool as well.
And I guess to lock it, you just
Okay, yeah, that's how you lock it.
That's pretty nice.
And so, yeah. I think I'm just going to
quickly Wait, can you use this as a
catapult? I'm now so curious about this.
Oh, come on. Can you use this as a
catapult, though?
Oh god, you can. Yes, you can. I nearly
just shattered my screen.
Okay. So,
uh yeah, I'm just going to quickly test
this on an apple. Okay, so I didn't have
any apples, you know, healthy. But, I do
have
carrots. Oh, yeah. Okay, 3
2 1
Okay, so that was the end of the video.
If you want one of these, just get them
in the description.
How about you just watch my other
unboxing videos, which I'm going to put
on screen right now, and also up there.
And yeah, guys.
Bye.